<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ezra Mechaber</title>
    <link>http://ezramechaber.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ezra Mechaber</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 21:53:49 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ezramechaber.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Portfolio</title>
      <link>http://ezramechaber.com/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 21:53:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezramechaber.com/social/</guid>
      <description>Since 2015, I&amp;rsquo;ve helped Precision Strategies tackle challenges for nonprofits, political campaigns, Fortune 50&amp;rsquo;s, and Silicon Valley startups.
We&amp;rsquo;ve helped influencers organize around trans rights: Laverne Cox promoting #StandWithGavin in support of Gavin Grimm. &amp;nbsp;
And helped a presidential candidate shout out One Direction: The boys are right. We need everyone&amp;#39;s help to get the planet moving in the right direction. http://t.co/rNQSBSmgJ8 #action1D
&amp;mdash; Hillary Clinton (@HillaryClinton) July 9, 2015  &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://ezramechaber.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 18:48:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezramechaber.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I help campaigns, non-profits, and companies do stuff—tell their story, recruit volunteers, raise money, launch new products—online.
From 2011 to 2015, I worked in the Obama White House’s Office of Digital Strategy, we worked to make it easier for citizens to interact with a massive federal bureaucracy:
 I helped grow and run the 29 million user We the People petitions platform, responding to petitioners on some thorny issues—and some fun ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://ezramechaber.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezramechaber.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Project 1 - Ei viderer tacimates pro, quem assum ea nam. Veritus omnesque eam te. Et natum mucius tamquam vel, ea dolorem volumus deterruisset nec. Graeci mentitum sea an, eu prima elaboraret est.   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Project 2 - An eripuit phaedrum qui, nec facer splendide ex, vel ea assum facilisi convenire. Te his neglegentur consectetuer.   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Project 3 - An alii quot tantas eum, doming platonem persecuti mea et, vim perpetua cotidieque delicatissimi in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>